[
  {
    "id": 1,
    "round": "round2",
    "subject": "Maths",
    "question": "Perimeter of Square",
    "ans": [
      "Volume of Sphere",
      "Volume of Sphere",
      "Volume of Sphere",
      "Volume of Sphere"
    ],
    "questionHindi": "गोले का आयतन",
    "ansHindi": [
      "Volume of Sphere",
      "Volume of Sphere",
      "Volume of Sphere",
      "Volume of Sphere"
    ],
    "correctAns": "4xa",
    "enable": true
  },
  {
    "id": 2,
    "subject": "Maths",
    "round": "round2",
    "question": "Volume of Cylinder",
    "ans": [
      "πR²h",
      "πr²h",
      "½π²rd",
      "⅓πr²h"
    ],
    "questionHindi": "बेलन का आयतन",
    "ansHindi": [
      "",
      "",
      "",
      ""
    ],
    "correctAns": "πr²h",
    "enable": true
  },
  {
    "id": 3,
    "subject": "Maths",
    "round": "round2",
    "question": "Volume of Cone",
    "ans": [
      "πr²h",
      "πD²h",
      "⅓πr²h",
      "⅔πr²h"
    ],
    "questionHindi": "शंकु का आयतन",
    "ansHindi": [
      "",
      "",
      "",
      ""
    ],
    "correctAns": "⅓πr²h4",
    "enable": false
  },
  {
    "id": 4,
    "subject": "Maths",
    "round": "round2",
    "question": "(x+a)(x+b)",
    "ans": [
      "x²-(a+b)x+ab",
      "x²(a+b)x+ab",
      "x²+(a+b)x-ab",
      "x²-(a-b)x-ab"
    ],
    "questionHindi": "",
    "ansHindi": [
      "",
      "",
      "",
      ""
    ],
    "correctAns": "x²(a+b)x+ab",
    "enable": true
  },
  {
    "id": 5,
    "subject": "Maths",
    "round": "round2",
    "question": "Semi-perimeter",
    "ans": [
      "(a+b-c)/2",
      "(a-b+c)/2",
      "(a+b+c)/2",
      "(a-b-c)/2"
    ],
    "questionHindi": "अर्द्धपरिमाप",
    "ansHindi": [
      "",
      "",
      "",
      ""
    ],
    "correctAns": "(a+b+c)/2",
    "enable": true
  },
  {
    "id": 6,
    "subject": "Maths",
    "round": "round2",
    "question": "Volume of Cuboid",
    "ans": [
      "axbxc",
      "l²xbxh",
      "lxaxb",
      "lxbxh"
    ],
    "questionHindi": "घनाभ का आयतन",
    "ansHindi": [
      "",
      "",
      "",
      ""
    ],
    "correctAns": "lxbxh",
    "enable": true
  },
  {
    "id": 7,
    "subject": "Maths",
    "round": "round2",
    "question": "(x+y)²",
    "ans": [
      "y²-2xy+x²",
      "x²+y²+2xy",
      "x²-2xy-y²",
      "x²+y²"
    ],
    "questionHindi": "",
    "ansHindi": [
      "",
      "",
      "",
      ""
    ],
    "correctAns": "x²+y²+2xy",
    "enable": true
  },
  {
    "id": 8,
    "subject": "Maths",
    "round": "round2",
    "question": "Volume of Sphere",
    "ans": [
      "Volume of Sphere",
      "Volume of Sphere",
      "Volume of Sphere",
      "Volume of Sphere"
    ],
    "questionHindi": "गोले का आयतन",
    "ansHindi": [
      "Volume of Sphere",
      "Volume of Sphere",
      "Volume of Sphere",
      "Volume of Sphere"
    ],
    "correctAns": "4/3 πr³",
    "enable": true
  },
  {
    "id": 9,
    "subject": "Maths",
    "round": "round2",
    "question": "x²-2xy+y²",
    "ans": [
      "(x-y)²",
      "(x+y)²",
      "(x²-y²)",
      "(x+y)(x-y)"
    ],
    "questionHindi": "",
    "ansHindi": [
      "",
      "",
      "",
      ""
    ],
    "correctAns": "(x-y)²",
    "enable": true
  },
  {
    "id": 10,
    "subject": "Maths",
    "round": "round2",
    "question": "x²-y²",
    "ans": [
      "(y-x)(y-x)",
      "(y-x)(x+y)",
      "(x-y)(x+y)",
      "(x+y)(x+y)"
    ],
    "questionHindi": "",
    "ansHindi": [
      "",
      "",
      "",
      ""
    ],
    "correctAns": "(x-y)(x+y)",
    "enable": true
  }
]